bitstatement.org 2016-05-02

# BIT - Your Single Source Provider For Document Delivery

### Privacy Policy

At BIT, we value the trust that our clients and their account holders place in us. We are committed to protecting the personal privacy of individuals that visit our web site and use our products and services.

The purpose of our Privacy Policy is to protect the privacy and confidentiality of our clients, and more specifically to protect the interests of our clients' account holders. We pledge that we will take the steps necessary to protect the privacy of all information shared with our company in the course of fulfilling your business needs with BIT's products and services.

#### Use of Cookies

Some areas of our website may use cookies. When we do set a cookie, it contains information we need for security, and allows us to 'time out' your authority to view certain information, or tell us what information we should give you on this visit. We place the cookie with instructions that it can only be sent to a server in our domain. A cookie cannot be used to extract data from your PC. We do not store any Access Code, User Id or Password in any cookie.

With most Internet Browsers, you can erase Cookies from your computer hard drive, block all Cookies, or receive a warning before a Cookie is stored. Please refer to your Browser instructions or help menu to learn more about these functions.

#### Non-Personal Information

We employ software programs to monitor and log all network traffic on our servers. We do this for site management and to identify attempts to upload, change or otherwise access our servers without authorization.

BIT also uses information collected on this site to help compile broad statistical trends that help us improve navigation and content. We use this non-personal information for internal statistical purposes and product evaluation only; it is not shared with unaffiliated third parties.

The information collected may include the domain and IP address you use while visiting our site, the date and time you access our site, and the pages you visit while you were at our site.

#### Personal Information

When you send us personally identifying information in an email or by filling out a form on our website, we use this information to fulfill or respond to your request. We may store these requests for future responses to you.

We do not sell or distribute personal information, including e-mail addresses collected via our eStatement application, to any third party. We will never utilize data obtained from individual account holders without the permission of both our client and the individual consumer. BIT will not reveal specific information about consumer accounts or other personally identifiable data to unaffiliated third parties for their independent use except when disclosure is required by law (e.g. subpoena, investigation of fraud, etc).

The management of BIT limits employee access to information to those with a business reason for knowing such information. We educate our employees on the importance of maintaining account holder confidentiality and we enforce our privacy policies with appropriate disciplinary procedures.

#### Security Procedures to Protect Information

With the support of VeriSign, BIT operates secure data networks protected by industry standard firewalls, encryption, and password protection. When institutions connect with our secure server, we employ Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protection, which encrypts or scrambles your data so that no one else can read it. The use of SSL does require version 4.0 or higher of Netscape or Microsoft Explorer browsers or the latest version of AOL.
